# **Trepov Viacheslav**

Ukraine, Kiev | 29.06.1987 | 093-587-23-41 | Telegram @slavon\_1212 | Mail: slava.trepov@gmail.com

# Linux administrator / DevOps Engineer 3 000 \$

## **Professional Summary**

Qualified IT-specialist with experience in administration \*nix servers (Linux, Freebsd), systems maintenance diagnosis and infrastructure planning. Extensive experience in remote administration and work with a variety of systems(Win/MacOS/Linux) and networks. Self-disciplined, flexible, confident and ready for new responsibilities. At the moment I'm only interested in working with Open Source Linux services

#### Skills

- Administration Servers: Linux (Ubuntu, Centos) / FreeBSD;
- Web Servers: Nginx / Haproxy;
- DB: Postgresql / Percona;
- Firewall: iptables / firewalld;
- Virtualization: kvm / proxmox / Vmware Esxi;
- Monitoring: Zabbix / LibreNMS / Prometheus / Grafana;
- Log: syslog / Loki;
- Configuration management: SaltStack, Ansible
- bash-scripting / python-scripting (junior)
- Git / github / gitlab / bitbucket;
- CI/CD: Jenkins;
- Containers: docker / docker-compose.

### Experience

#### **DevOps Engineer, Everstake**

09/2022 to 05/2023

#### Responsibilities:

Execution tasks for network operations (setup nodes, researching, troubleshooting, updating, configure monitoring), read discord chats,

communicate system requirements to software development teams, noc engineers. Skills:

Strong Linux (Ubuntu), Ansible, Zabbix, Grafana, Haproxy, Cloudflare, Work/debug with API curl, websocket, Iptables, Docker, Docker-compose, Github, Gitlab, Bash-scripting, Python-scripting

#### **DevOps Engineer, Artdock**

10/2021 to 08/2022

Responsibilities:

Communicate system requirements to noc engineers,

setup nodes, troubleshooting, updating, configure monitoring, slack/discord chats.

Skills:

Mdadm soft-RAID / ZFS / Saltstack / Zabbix / LibreNMS / Prometheus / Grafana / Bash scripting / Python scripting / Git / Jenkins

#### Senior linux administrator, Cyfral Service

08/2018 to 09/2021

Responsibilities:

Support and administrative Linux/FreeBSD servers (setup nodes, troubleshooting, updating). Administrative Supervisors (Proxmox, KVM(Qemu), Vmware)

Skills:

Zabbix / Squid / Bind / Bash-scripting / Backups

Education

APEPS department of Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

09/2003 to 09/2008

# completed courses (certificates)

- Implementation of network infrastructure based on Linux systems;
- Red Hat System Administration. Network services and security;
- System Administration Unix (FreeBSD).